https://www.equinux.com/privacy

Store
VPN Tracker (Mac)
VPN Tracker World Connect (Mac, iOS)
Mail Designer 365 (Mac)
tizi
TV Pro (iOS, Apple TV, Android)
Live TV (Mac, iOS, Apple TV)
TV Pro Mediathek (iOS, Apple TV)
TV Pro (iOS, Apple TV, Android)
Live TV (Mac, iOS, Apple TV)
VPN Tracker (Mac)
VPN Tracker World Connect (Mac, iOS)
Mail Designer Pro 365 (Mac)
tizi
LEGAL INFORMATION · RECHTLICHE GRUNDLAGEN
Privacy Policy · Datenschutzerklärung
We secure your personal informationThe privacy of our customers is very important to equinux. We have taken appropriate measures to ensure the security of all customer data. equinux is committed to protecting the information you share with us. This Privacy Policy explains how equinux processes information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify a person ("Personal Information"). This data is generated by the use of our website and our services. All equinux products and services are fully compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union (GDPR).Who is responsible for data collection and processing?The equinux Group collects and processes your data as the responsible authority.The equinux Group consists of the following companies  (collectively referred to as “equinux”):equinux AG, Dr.-Johann-Heitzer-Str. 4, 85757 Karlsfeld/Munich, Germanyequinux USA, Inc., 533 Airport Blvd. Suite 400, Burlingame, CA 94010, USATOWER ONE GmbH, Dr.-Johann-Heitzer-Str. 4, 85757 Karlsfeld/Munich, GermanyLive TV GmbH, Dr.-Johann-Heitzer-Str. 4, 85757 Karlsfeld/Munich, GermanyThe data protection officer for all companies of the equinux Group can be reached at privacy@equinux.com. What data is collected and processed about me? And why?With equinux you are the customer and not the product. Our services are not free of charge because we don’t sell your data. Data collection and sale or trading of this information is not our business model, unlike providers such as Facebook, Google, XING, etc.All data collection and processing is done for specific purposes to run our apps, products and services. Personal data may be required to  fulfill technical requirements, contractual requirements or explicit user wishes. Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person. Any entry of personal or business data expressly takes place on a voluntary basis. Here are some examples of the types of personal information equinux may collect and how we may use it:1. By visiting our websiteFor technical reasons, certain data must be collected and stored when using our website, e.g. the date and duration of the visit, the pages visited, the type of browser and operating system used and which page you came from.2. By creating an accountYou have the option of creating a customer account to use our products and services (referred to as an “equinux ID” or other product name-related ID such as TV Pro ID, Mail Designer ID, VPN Tracker ID). This can be used, for example, tomake a purchasedownload or start a demo versionactivate a productuse cloud storage features (e.g. to sync settings  between devices)to redeem a product codeWhen creating an equinux ID, we ask for as little data as possible, such as name, email address, country. Other personal information is optional, but may be required for specific purposes (e.g. we need your  the delivery address for shipping). To confirm your account, we will send you a verification email. When you’ve created an equinux ID, we may contact you by email, if you permit us to do so. Reasons for contacting you include:B. Account-related informationC. Information by newsletterTo learn more about the content of these types of communications and how to unsubscribe, please see the section: How will I be contacted?3. By making a purchaseWhen you make a purchase on our website, we collect information such as your full name, username, email address, contact address, billing address, credit card, and any other information required to complete a financial transaction. Based on your purchase, we may contact you by mail or email unless you object to such use. The reason for contacting you is:A. Purchase-related informationB. Account-related informationC. Information by newsletterTo learn more about the content of these types of communications and how to unsubscribe, please see the section: How will I be contacted?4. By subscribing to our newsletterYou can subscribe to our newsletters on our website and we’ll need your email address for this. To confirm your email address, we will send you a verification email. Based on your newsletter registration we can contact you by email. The reason for contacting us is:C. Information by newsletterTo learn more about the content of these types of communications and how to unsubscribe, please see the section: How will I be contacted?5. By using an equinux productIf you use an equinux product, we may collect information about your use, such as: your user account information, the time and date of the last login, your IP address, and information about the device you use to log in. equinux will use such information to improve our products, to fulfill your requests, to supply the corresponding product or service, or to prevent fraud. A customer account may be required to use the product. Based on your usage, we may be able to contact you by email, if you allow us to do so. The reason for contacting you is:B. Account-related informationC. Information by newsletterTo learn more about the content of these types of communications and how to unsubscribe, please see the section: How will I be contacted?6. By contacting usYou can contact us if you have a question about a product, a purchase, or other topics. As a part of this you can provide us with personal information. All information you provide to us is voluntary. It is not necessary to provide us with personal information. However, if you do not provide us with certain information, we may not be able to help you. All information you provide us may be used to respond to your request and to improve our products. You consent to the processing of this data for this purpose by reaching out to us. This consent can be revoked at any time.7. Use as a referenceWith your explicit consent, we may list you as a reference on our website. If we mention you on our website, it is possible that personal data will be used. The scope will of course be discussed prior to publication. If you would like to update or delete a reference listing, please contact us at privacy@equinux.com.How will I be contacted?We typically contact you as customers and users for three different reasons:A. Purchase-related informationIf you have purchased a product, we will send you purchase related information by email. This may include the following:Purchase confirmationsInformation about the renewal or expiration of a productNecessary information for account managementPurchase-related information is contract-relevant information and therefore not a newsletter. You can not unsubscribe from purchase-related information. Purchase-related information is sent only within the scope of an active product.B. Account-related informationIf you have created a customer account and use it as part of a product, we may send you account-related information, if you allow us to do so. For example, this information may include the following topics:Information about new versions or features of the productInformation about the download or demo versionsTips and tricks to help you get the most out of your productAccount-related information is customer-specific information. This information can be unsubscribed at any time. To do so, click on the corresponding button or link in the email you have received. No costs arise that exceed the basic costs of transmission.C. Information by newsletterIf you are subscribed to our newsletter, we may send you newsletters from time to time. As an example these newsletters may cover the following topics:Information about offers or promosInformation about new products from usInformation about similar and or compatible products of our partnersYou can unsubscribe from newsletters at any time. To do so, click on the corresponding button or link in the email you have received. No costs arise that exceed the basic costs of transmission.Will data be shared? If so, with whom?Data storage and processing by companies of the equinux groupFor the execution of the contract and the use of product functionalities, your data can be stored and processed by all equinux Group companies under this privacy policy.Data storage and processing by third partiesIn a networked world, companies work together to provide the best possible products and services. We’re no different: For the sale and operation of our products, we rely on specialised processors that enable us to offer you the best possible experience. These include payment service providers, cloud storage and processing operators or shipping service providers. External service providers who process data on our behalf are carefully selected and subject to strict contractual requirements. They work according to our instructions and have to adhere to strict technical and organizational measures to protect any data. Let’s be clear: We do not sell your data to these service providers, the data will only be transmitted to third parties under this privacy policy.Data access for legal reasonsIn specific cases, personal data may be shared with professional advisers (for example, accountants, lawyers, business consultants) or government agencies (such as tax offices, regulators). This is solely for the purpose of receiving professional advice, reviewing and defending legal claims, such as in litigation or out of court proceedings, in the context of regulatory investigations or proceedings, or as a result of other legal obligations.Sale of the company or productYour personal data may also be transferred to a third party if the company or part of it is sold. Since the sale of a company or product always includes the associated customer data, it would be transferred in this case. Any potential buyer is required to handle the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Data transmission abroadequinux is a global group of companies with subsidiaries, business processes, management structures and technical systems, some of which are located abroad. This means that your personal information may be transferred to other countries, possibly outside the EU. In other countries, there are other legal provisions regarding data protection. equinux makes sure that adequate protection for your data is ensured. This includes, for example, the use of standard agreements approved by the competent authorities and the requirement to take appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data. By entering your personal data, you agree to this transmission abroad.How long will my data be stored?We only store your data for as long as it is needed (for example, under a contract / purchase) or as long as it is required by law. So we keep your data in the context of a contract / purchase at least until the complete termination of the contract. After that, the data is kept for the duration of statutory retention periods. When you exercise your right to be forgotten, your data will be erased, except for transaction data, which we are required to keep due to legal reasons such as tax laws, as well as any data necessary to fulfill existing contracts.How secure is my data?We use technical and organizational security measures to protect the data you provide against loss, destruction or access by unauthorized persons through accidental or intentional manipulation. We constantly improve our security measures based on the current state-of-the-art.Are cookies used? Which known analytic tools are used?When using our websiteWe use cookies on our website for analysis purposes. Cookies are small text files in which data can be stored on your device and are used by us to improve our website and services. In most cases these are so-called "session cookies", which are deleted after leaving our website. However, to a certain extent, these cookies also pass on information that automatically identifies you via the data stored in the cookies. The information is used to improve our services and speed up your access to the website. You can prevent cookies being set by adjusting the privacy settings in your browser. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of the website.Google AnalyticsOur website and our apps use Google Analytics, a web analysis service from Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as “Google“. Google Analytics usescookies to facilitate an analysis of your use of the site.The information generated by these cookies, such as time, place and frequency of your visits to our site, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google’s location in the US and stored there.We use Google Analytics with an IP anonymization feature on our website. This means Google abbreviates and thereby anonymizes your IP address before transferring it from member states of the European Union or signatory states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.Google will use this information to evaluate your usage of our site, to compile reports on website activity for us, and to provide other services related to app-, website- and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if this is required by law or to the extent this data is processed by third parties on Google´s behalf.Google states that it will in never associate your IP address with other data held by Google. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software accordingly. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website.Google also offers a disabling option for the most common browsers, thus providing you with greater control over the data which is collected and processed by Google. If you enable this option, no information regarding your website visit is transmitted to Google Analytics. However, the activation does not prevent the transmission of information to us or to any other web analytics services we may use. For more information about the disabling option provided by Google, and how to enable this option, visit https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enAs an alternative to the above mentioned browser plug-in or when using mobile devices, you can disable the collection of the information generated by the cookie by clicking the following link: Disable Google Analytics.An opt-out cookie will be then stored that disables the collection of your information for future visits of our websites.Further information is available here: https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html or https://policies.google.com/?hl=gb (general informationen on Google Analytics and privacy).Use of Google AdWordsBy using the online advertising program Google AdWords from Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; hereinafter referred to as "Google"), advertisements are displayed and sorted thematically based on the keywords used in a Google search. To do this, Google sets a cookie in the browser when a user clicks on an advertisement in the Google search network or advertising network. The legal basis for this is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.Click here to opt out of this: www.google.com/ads/preferencesUsing the AdWords cookie and conversion methods, Google can assess the number of people who choose an advertised offer after clicking on a relevant AdWords advertisement. Where Google's advertisements refer to equinux sites, Google provides us with statistics about the number of purchases that users make after clicking on a Google AdWords advertisement.If you want to opt out: You can set your browser so that it blocks cookies originating from googleadservices.com or from third parties in general. You can also delete the Google conversion cookie “Conversion” in your browser’s cookie settings.Use of Google Doubleclickequinux also uses Google Remarketing based on Doubleclick from Google Inc. for placing interest-based advertising. The Doubleclick cookie uses a pseudonymous identification number to check the pages displayed and to assign advertisements. The information about displayed pages generated by this cookie is forwarded to Google's server for evaluation and storage. The legal basis for this is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.Google's privacy policy is available at www.google.de/intl/en/policies/privacyIf you want to opt out: www.google.com/ads/preferencesUse of Bing AdsThis website uses Bing Ads, a program provided by Microsoft Corporation, One Microsoft Way, Redmond, WA 98052-6399, USA. Bing Ads places a cookie on your computer, if you were directed to our website via a Microsoft Bing Ad or another website of the Microsoft Bing advertising network. Thereby, Microsoft and we can recognise that someone has clicked an ad, was forwarded to our website and reached a certain landing page before (conversion page).  If you do not want to participate in the tracking, you can reject the necessary placement of the cookie (’opt out’) – e.g. by browser settings preventing the automatic placement of cookies in general or via the settings on the following page: https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings/signedout?lang=en-GB. Further information about data protection and the cookies used by Microsoft Bing can be found on the Microsoft website:  https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-gb/privacystatement.Use of Twitter AdsWe use the conversion tracking provided by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA (’Twitter’). This tracking records when a user of our website clicks on an ad placed by Twitter. Thereby, we and Twitter can retrace whether a SignUp has taken place. A personal identification does not take place. Furthermore, we use ’Tailored Audiences’ provided by Twitter. By this, we can deliver targeted advertisings to users of our website. For this purpose, Twitter uses a code-snippet (Tag), which we have integrated into our website. No personal data are recorded. ’Tailored Audiences’ is also used to create look-alike targeting lists.In Twitter’s privacy statement you can find further information on data protection (https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en). You can adjust your settings for tailored ads via the following link: https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads. In addition, Twitter supports ’Do Not Track’ (DNT). If you have activated this option in your browser, Twitter will not receive any browser related information (browser cookie ID) from its advertising partners for tailored customization of ads.What are my rights as a user and how do I make use of them?As a customer, we grant you all the rights associated with your data. To help you exercise these rights, here is an overview of how and where you can exercise your rights in our systems:InformationYou can request information about what data is stored about you.If you would like to know what data is stored about you, you can do so at the following link: http://store.equinux.com/privacy. Correction, deletion and restriction (blocking)You may request the correction, deletion and restriction of the processing (blocking) of your personal data as long as this is permitted by law and within the scope of an existing contractual relationship.You can update the personal information in your account at http://my.equinux.com.If you wish to delete or restrict / restrict your personal information, you can do so at http://store.equinux.com/privacy.Please note that after deletion you will irrevocably lose full access to all equinux services. You can no longer log in to your account and use equinux products with this account. Even after you've deleted your account, we may need to retain some data for a specified period of time to comply with regulatory requirements.In the case of current subscriptions (also called continuous debt), it is only possible to delete your complete data at the end of the term, so that we can fulfill our contractual services. Should you wish a deletion before the end of the term, we need a disclaimer from you. In this case, please contact our support.Transferability of dataYou have the right to transferability of the data that you have submitted to us based on consent or under a contract. To transfer your data, you can download it from http://store.equinux.com/privacy and continue to use it according to your wishes.If you wish to review the data stored about you, you can access it at: http://store.equinux.com/privacy. If you have any further questions regarding use of your personal data, please email us at privacy@equinux.com. If you would like to correct personal data, you may do so by logging into your account at http://my.equinux.com.Unsubscribe from communication with usYou can opt out of advertising messages at any time with future effect (advertising opt-out). Not every communication you receive from us is a "advertising" communication. For more information on how we communicate and how to unsubscribe, see "How will I be contacted?"Further questions?In case you have further questions regarding the use of your personal data, you can contact us at privacy@equinux.com. How up to date is this data privacy information?We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. You should visit this page occasionally to ensure you agree with any changes to this policy. We may notify you of significant changes to this policy by email or within an equinux App you are using.Current version: May 2018App Specific InformationVPN TrackerConnection Safe: When you upload your connections to Connection Safe, we store a strongly encrypted copy of your connection on secure my.vpntracker servers. Only you will be able to access and decrypt connections stored in your Connection Safe, so be sure to keep your encryption password and recovery key safe. We also store metadata that lets us sync your connection, including the name, the last time you synced the connection and the version of the encryption scheme that was used.TV ProTV Pro anonymously aggregates the number of people who have added a show to their watchlist. The most popular shows are displayed as the “User Tips” – the favorite shows as voted for by all TV Pro users.Live TVLive Ratings: Live TV uses anonymized usage data from the Live TV app to provide the audience ratings. You agree to this use of the data as a user of the Live TV app.Live TV Location: Live TV needs the location to calculate and return the ratings based on your country. This data will also be collected anonymously. By activating the location feature you agree to this anonymized data transfer.
Who we are
Business Mission
Management
How we work
Our team
Product Overview
Directions
Investor
